[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "How old are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Forty-seven.", "answer_tokens": ["Forty-seven", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "You're -- you're a year old than me, and you look like this?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "--", "you", "'re", "a", "year", "old", "than", "me", ",", "and", "you", "look", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Under your suit, I know that you look like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Under", "your", "suit", ",", "I", "know", "that", "you", "look", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Do you look that under your suit?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "look", "that", "under", "your", "suit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "PhotoShop.", "answer_tokens": ["PhotoShop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What did you think when you heard?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "when", "you", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, I literally had a week out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "literally", "had", "a", "week", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What was going through your mind having had that odd connection?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "having", "had", "that", "odd", "connection", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, I mean, my first response was that these families will maybe have some sort of closure to the extent that anyone can really have closure with the kind of things that families have gone through.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "my", "first", "response", "was", "that", "these", "families", "will", "maybe", "have", "some", "sort", "of", "closure", "to", "the", "extent", "that", "anyone", "can", "really", "have", "closure", "with", "the", "kind", "of", "things", "that", "families", "have", "gone", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "And what's the first thing you did?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "'s", "the", "first", "thing", "you", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, I went down to Times Square because I got a -- I just had a sense that people would be gathering and sharing this moment in history.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "went", "down", "to", "Times", "Square", "because", "I", "got", "a", "--", "I", "just", "had", "a", "sense", "that", "people", "would", "be", "gathering", "and", "sharing", "this", "moment", "in", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "When you knew that you had been on a plane that had been used as -- as a dry run, how does it make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "knew", "that", "you", "had", "been", "on", "a", "plane", "that", "had", "been", "used", "as", "--", "as", "a", "dry", "run", ",", "how", "does", "it", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I got on that flight.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "got", "on", "that", "flight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April"]}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "And what is it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "I think it's an April Fool's joke.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "an", "April", "Fool", "'s", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Did you have any memory of these guys being on the plane?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "memory", "of", "these", "guys", "being", "on", "the", "plane", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Have you ever been tempted to have a proper run yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "been", "tempted", "to", "have", "a", "proper", "run", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, you know, I -- you know, I loved politics more as a younger man.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "loved", "politics", "more", "as", "a", "younger", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "-- you have to be a conservative when you get older, right?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "have", "to", "be", "a", "conservative", "when", "you", "get", "older", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, it's funny.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "In what way?", "question_tokens": ["In", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "So, it wouldn't actually be damaging, would it?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "it", "would", "n't", "actually", "be", "damaging", ",", "would", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, that's true.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Does -- and what of that prospect?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "--", "and", "what", "of", "that", "prospect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", ":", "CC", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I love -- I helped Trump run.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "--", "I", "helped", "Trump", "run", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 245, "question": "But, also, he was able to stand back at the end and say, \"Well, I forced out the truth,\" you know?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "also", ",", "he", "was", "able", "to", "stand", "back", "at", "the", "end", "and", "say", ",", "``", "Well", ",", "I", "forced", "out", "the", "truth", ",", "''", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "\"Declare a victory, and get off the field.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Declare", "a", "victory", ",", "and", "get", "off", "the", "field", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "When you saw Matt say that, did you share a slight disappointment for President Obama or no?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "Matt", "say", "that", ",", "did", "you", "share", "a", "slight", "disappointment", "for", "President", "Obama", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I think it -- I think it's really hard.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "really", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Don't you play, boy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "play", ",", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE).", "answer_tokens": ["(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "I mean, what a problem I'd love to have, Mr. Lowe?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "a", "problem", "I", "'d", "love", "to", "have", ",", "Mr.", "Lowe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Listen, nobody is going to throw any charity events for me on this subject.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "nobody", "is", "going", "to", "throw", "any", "charity", "events", "for", "me", "on", "this", "subject", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Lowe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "I mean, is it -- is it a double-edged sword being impossibly good looking?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "it", "--", "is", "it", "a", "double-edged", "sword", "being", "impossibly", "good", "looking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "See, by answering that question I implicitly agree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["See", ",", "by", "answering", "that", "question", "I", "implicitly", "agree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "What are you about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, part of me is -- I'm a lot nerdier.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "part", "of", "me", "is", "--", "I", "'m", "a", "lot", "nerdier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "In what way?", "question_tokens": ["In", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "-- than you think.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "than", "you", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I think I'm amazed that that launched so many people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "amazed", "that", "that", "launched", "so", "many", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fred Ruse"]}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", ":", "WP", "RB", "``", "NNP", "PRP", ",", "''", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "``", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 337, "question": "I mean, no movie could have ever launched quite as many huge stars as that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "no", "movie", "could", "have", "ever", "launched", "quite", "as", "many", "huge", "stars", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, the casting -- the man who cast that movie, whose voice was on the clip we just heard is a man named Fred Ruse, (ph) who cast \"Godfather I,\" \"Godfather II,\" and \"Star Wars,\" and \"American Graffiti,\" and \"The Outsiders.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "casting", "--", "the", "man", "who", "cast", "that", "movie", ",", "whose", "voice", "was", "on", "the", "clip", "we", "just", "heard", "is", "a", "man", "named", "Fred", "Ruse", ",", "(", "ph", ")", "who", "cast", "``", "Godfather", "I", ",", "''", "``", "Godfather", "II", ",", "''", "and", "``", "Star", "Wars", ",", "''", "and", "``", "American", "Graffiti", ",", "''", "and", "``", "The", "Outsiders", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Do you -- do you stay in touch with any of that cast?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "do", "you", "stay", "in", "touch", "with", "any", "of", "that", "cast", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Friends with them?", "question_tokens": ["Friends", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNPS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "You know, it's more like the people that you go to college with, and who were in your dorm.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "more", "like", "the", "people", "that", "you", "go", "to", "college", "with", ",", "and", "who", "were", "in", "your", "dorm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Are there any you would just ring up for a chat?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "any", "you", "would", "just", "ring", "up", "for", "a", "chat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "It's quite a barbaric business, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "quite", "a", "barbaric", "business", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Really to get a part of this, you have to get a little damaged.", "answer_tokens": ["Really", "to", "get", "a", "part", "of", "this", ",", "you", "have", "to", "get", "a", "little", "damaged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "And you can almost chart the parallel.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "you", "can", "almost", "chart", "the", "parallel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "It's fascinating, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "fascinating", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Yes -- no.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "--", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "That that's why so many people that go through that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["That", "that", "'s", "why", "so", "many", "people", "that", "go", "through", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I -- like I said, I really believe that it's so fulfilling to connect with an audience on stage, on -- on screen; however you're doing it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "like", "I", "said", ",", "I", "really", "believe", "that", "it", "'s", "so", "fulfilling", "to", "connect", "with", "an", "audience", "on", "stage", ",", "on", "--", "on", "screen", ";", "however", "you", "'re", "doing", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "You didn't actually do that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "actually", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "That's what you actually did?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "you", "actually", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Pentagon"]}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "And then what happened?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I did a little research, and I came up with a phone number, and I called her at the Pentagon.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "a", "little", "research", ",", "and", "I", "came", "up", "with", "a", "phone", "number", ",", "and", "I", "called", "her", "at", "the", "Pentagon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "You didn't?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "And?", "question_tokens": ["And", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "The rest is history.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "rest", "is", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "I mean, not only women who were the hottest dates to be had, you were on a bit of a mission, weren't you, to be like the stud of your generation?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "not", "only", "women", "who", "were", "the", "hottest", "dates", "to", "be", "had", ",", "you", "were", "on", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "mission", ",", "were", "n't", "you", ",", "to", "be", "like", "the", "stud", "of", "your", "generation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "My motto into this day is: go big, or go home.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "motto", "into", "this", "day", "is", ":", "go", "big", ",", "or", "go", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Do you think everybody has that devil in them basically?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "everybody", "has", "that", "devil", "in", "them", "basically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "You know what, I'm going to agree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "agree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Which one would you least rather go through again?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "would", "you", "least", "rather", "go", "through", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "That's the definition of a Sophie's choice.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "definition", "of", "a", "Sophie", "'s", "choice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "If I could say to you you've got to go through one of these again, which would you least rather go through again?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "say", "to", "you", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "go", "through", "one", "of", "these", "again", ",", "which", "would", "you", "least", "rather", "go", "through", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, I would take the sex tape off the list, because it led me to get sober, which changed my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "take", "the", "sex", "tape", "off", "the", "list", ",", "because", "it", "led", "me", "to", "get", "sober", ",", "which", "changed", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Do you understand why people are obsessed with celebrities doing that kind of thing, or being caught doing that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "why", "people", "are", "obsessed", "with", "celebrities", "doing", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", ",", "or", "being", "caught", "doing", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "It's a culture.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "culture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Do you look at other people and enjoy their own scandals, downfalls and so on, in the way that others have enjoyed yours over the years?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "look", "at", "other", "people", "and", "enjoy", "their", "own", "scandals", ",", "downfalls", "and", "so", "on", ",", "in", "the", "way", "that", "others", "have", "enjoyed", "yours", "over", "the", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Once you go through your turn in the barrel, you have a unique perspective on it.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", "you", "go", "through", "your", "turn", "in", "the", "barrel", ",", "you", "have", "a", "unique", "perspective", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "When you see someone like him resolutely refusing to play the traditional game, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "someone", "like", "him", "resolutely", "refusing", "to", "play", "the", "traditional", "game", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "There's a part of me that admires that, that admires resolutely living his life.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "part", "of", "me", "that", "admires", "that", ",", "that", "admires", "resolutely", "living", "his", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Do you worry about him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "about", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Oh yes, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Do you fear that one day you're going to wake up and something awful will have happened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fear", "that", "one", "day", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "wake", "up", "and", "something", "awful", "will", "have", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "You know, I hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Why did you need to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "need", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Well, I think I was probably living a life that was not as satisfying as I was pretending it to be.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "was", "probably", "living", "a", "life", "that", "was", "not", "as", "satisfying", "as", "I", "was", "pretending", "it", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "But when you actually get it, it's not quite what it's cracked up to be?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "actually", "get", "it", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "quite", "what", "it", "'s", "cracked", "up", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Also, I think it's probably really satisfying for a while.", "answer_tokens": ["Also", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "probably", "really", "satisfying", "for", "a", "while", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Would you try everything once?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "try", "everything", "once", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Where did you draw the line?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "draw", "the", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I didn't -- this is the '80s.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "--", "this", "is", "the", "'80s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Was it that good?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "that", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "A lot of it was.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Do you ever miss it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "miss", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "If I thought I could go out and do what I used to do and have fun, I would do it in two seconds.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "thought", "I", "could", "go", "out", "and", "do", "what", "I", "used", "to", "do", "and", "have", "fun", ",", "I", "would", "do", "it", "in", "two", "seconds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Or was it cathartic?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "it", "cathartic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "OWE: It was great.", "answer_tokens": ["OWE", ":", "It", "was", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NN", ",", "''", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Tell me about Cheryl, your wife, because she came along just when you need someone like her, didn't she?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "Cheryl", ",", "your", "wife", ",", "because", "she", "came", "along", "just", "when", "you", "need", "someone", "like", "her", ",", "did", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Well, when I met her -- I met her and she was my makeup artist on \"Bad Influence,\" a movie that I did, a good movie.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "I", "met", "her", "--", "I", "met", "her", "and", "she", "was", "my", "makeup", "artist", "on", "``", "Bad", "Influence", ",", "''", "a", "movie", "that", "I", "did", ",", "a", "good", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cheryl"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "For someone who doesn't know her, what are her qualities that particularly got you?", "question_tokens": ["For", "someone", "who", "does", "n't", "know", "her", ",", "what", "are", "her", "qualities", "that", "particularly", "got", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "She saw me unlike any other woman that had been in my orbit for years.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "saw", "me", "unlike", "any", "other", "woman", "that", "had", "been", "in", "my", "orbit", "for", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "What were you thinking when she did that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "thinking", "when", "she", "did", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "I was -- that I was the biggest loser ever, that I had blown this chance with somebody who truly loved me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "that", "I", "was", "the", "biggest", "loser", "ever", ",", "that", "I", "had", "blown", "this", "chance", "with", "somebody", "who", "truly", "loved", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "When you see contemporaries, many of them, who fall off the rails and go through wives and women and just never seem to find this kind of contentment, do you feel very, very lucky that you just managed to stumble across somebody that was perfect for you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "contemporaries", ",", "many", "of", "them", ",", "who", "fall", "off", "the", "rails", "and", "go", "through", "wives", "and", "women", "and", "just", "never", "seem", "to", "find", "this", "kind", "of", "contentment", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "very", ",", "very", "lucky", "that", "you", "just", "managed", "to", "stumble", "across", "somebody", "that", "was", "perfect", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "You mean, we haven't been on TV?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", ",", "we", "have", "n't", "been", "on", "TV", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "Yeah, we were off the air for a couple months, but now we're back.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "we", "were", "off", "the", "air", "for", "a", "couple", "months", ",", "but", "now", "we", "'re", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "You knew that, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "knew", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "No, I did not (EXPLETIVE DELETED) know that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "not", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "know", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "How long have I not been (EXPLETIVE DELETED) on television?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "have", "I", "not", "been", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "on", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Rob, this is good news.", "answer_tokens": ["Rob", ",", "this", "is", "good", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "What was the truth?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "The truth was -- and I think people who work for big corporations will get this.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "truth", "was", "--", "and", "I", "think", "people", "who", "work", "for", "big", "corporations", "will", "get", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Do you ever regret it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "regret", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "The greatest moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["The", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Listen, I've been blessed.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "blessed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1999"]}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "Which era is when you've been at your happiest?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "era", "is", "when", "you", "'ve", "been", "at", "your", "happiest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "1999 till now.", "answer_tokens": ["1999", "till", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110506pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "The business?", "question_tokens": ["The", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]